Serafin Dericks

WEB DEVELOPER

Profile

+54 2227 541191

tdsserafin@gmail.com

German living in Argentina

Links

LinkedIn

GitHub

Skills

HTML & CSS

React.js

Redux

Node.js

Express

Postgres

Sequelize

Scrum

Lenguages

Spanish - Native

English - B2/C1

German - A2

Hobbies

- I shelter stray cats and on some occasions I also adopt them.
- I like learning about robotics using Arduino.
- Trading and investing.

Summary

A 20 years old fast learner, hard worker, and team player web developer with solid experience and confidence in his skills that's seeking a job to improve even more as a rising professional and provide agile solutions using React, Redux, Node.js, Express, Postgres, and Sequelize among others.

Employment History

FullStack developer for CTH.

NOVEMBER 2021 - PRESENT

I am part of a team on the final stage of a Bootcamp at Henry Academy where we are doing a big web application working as a team.

The project is called "Coding To Help" or CTL in which we are making templates with different functionalities and designs for different Non-Gubernamental Organizations based on their needs.

My main contributions were setting the DB, making most of the back routes, to do responsive components, the full deployment, and also some integrations like MercadoPago and Paypal donations.

Developer experience on personal projects

MARCH 2021 - PRESENT

Most of my programming projects were done by using all the technologies mentioned above in my summary across multiple APIs, third-party integrations, and databases.

Since they were personal projects I had to do the frontend, backend, and the DB.

Some of those projects are:

- -Tasty Meals Done Dirty Cheap: A SPA with an elegant design where the user can search, upload, filter, and search among +5000 recipes and also learn how to cook them step by step.
- -Heavy Weather: A weather forecast application that you can use to look at the weather conditions in real-time all around the globe, also gives you detailed information about the city you searched.

Currently working on geolocalization integration and an interactive map.

-Gotta Map 'em All: Basically a Pokedex that I did as one of my first full stack projects. It does everything a pokemon wiki will let you do, search for pokemon, see their stats and types, and also create new pokemon.

Education

Computer Science Degree. University of Buenos Aires

NOVEMBER 2018 - PRESENT

I've already done a good part of the career studies plan and I'm still enrolled with acceptable grades.

Full-stack web developer certificate. Henry Academy Bootcamp

AUGUST 2021 - NOVEMBER 2021

An intensive programming Bootcamp in which I learned a lot about both web development and teamwork in where I developed many personal and requested projects. This Bootcamp gave me approximately 850 hours of coding.